<projects>
  <project id="pr101">
    <title>Online Dynamic Web Designing Tool</title>
    <technology>ASP.Net, C#, jQuery, Javascript, Bootstrap, MSSQL Server</technology>
    <imagepath>/img/portfolios/web/image-not-available.png</imagepath>
    <category>web</category>
    <description>
      This project was completed in B.Tech in a team of 5 members and the aim of this project was
      to provide a way to the non-technical person ability to develop website.
    </description>
  </project>
  <project id="pr102">
    <title>A website like Freelancer.com</title>
    <technology>ASP.Net, C#, jQuery, Javascript, Bootstrap, MSSQL Server</technology>
    <imagepath>/img/portfolios/web/image-not-available.png</imagepath>
    <category>web</category>
    <description>
      This project is the same as Freelancer.com which includes two main functions like Hire and Work.
      We developed this as a simple application during the B.Tech Industrial Training program in team of 4 members.
    </description>
  </project>
  <project id="pr103">
    <title>Claim Ruler</title>
    <technology>ASP.Net MVC 5, C#, jQuery, Javascript, Bootstrap, MSSQL Server, Database First Approach</technology>
    <imagepath>/img/portfolios/web/1.png</imagepath>
    <category>web</category>
    <description>
      This is a CRM project built on top of technologies like ASP.Net MVC, jQuery, Javascript etc and provides users facility to create Claims.
    </description>
  </project>
  <project id="pr104">
    <title>Street 2 Media</title>
    <technology>ASP.Net MVC, C#, jQuery, Javascript, Bootstrap, SQL Server</technology>
    <imagepath>/img/portfolios/web/2.png</imagepath>
    <category>web</category>
    <description>
      Put your photos and videos in front of the media and get paid! Register today and download. All the uploaded photos will be reviewed by Collaborators and will be displayed privately so that public users can pay and download.
    </description>
  </project>
  <project id="pr105">
    <title>iHRM</title>
    <technology>ASP.Net MVC, C#, jQuery, Angular.Js, Bootstrap, SQL Server</technology>
    <imagepath>/img/portfolios/web/3.png</imagepath>
    <category>web</category>
    <description>
      iHRM, an advanced leading software to manage Human Resource for a company. This project is built to provide the company a facility to create, update, delete users manage the user attendance etc.
    </description>
  </project>
  <project id="pr106">
    <title>Expense Management</title>
    <technology>Ionic, Angular.Js, Node.Js, MongoDb</technology>
    <imagepath>/img/portfolios/mobile/1.png</imagepath>
    <category>mobile</category>
    <description>
      This app is built using Ionic framework and using Node.Js service for authentication and back-end query and MongoDb is used for database storage.
    </description>
  </project>
  <project id="pr107">
    <title>Parse resume from Google Drive</title>
    <technology>ASP.Net, C#, jQuery, Javascript, Bootstrap, MSSQL Server</technology>
    <imagepath>/img/portfolios/web/drive.png</imagepath>
    <category>web</category>
    <description>
      This project uses Google Drive API to access the drive folder and reads the .doc and .docx files from the directory. It extracts the text from each file like Name, Degree, Technology, Skills etc and stores in SQL database. Admin can visit the page to view all the parsed resumes.
    </description>
  </project>
  <project id="pr108">
    <title>MowRichmond.com</title>
    <technology>Node.Js, ExpressJs, Mongodb, jQuery, Javascript, Bootstrap, Stripe Payment Gateway</technology>
    <imagepath>/img/portfolios/web/mow.png</imagepath>
    <category>web</category>
    <description>
      This website is running live in Richmond city of USA and using this site, users are able to search their address, register theirself for mow service and get the mow service weekly or monthly.
      It uses Stripe Payment Gateway for payment processing work and site is running at HTTPS protocol and uses SSL certificate.
    </description>
  </project>
  <project id="pr109">
    <title>Lets Chat</title>
    <technology>Ionic, AngularJs, Mongodb, Angular Bootstrap</technology>
    <imagepath>/img/portfolios/mobile/chat.png</imagepath>
    <category>mobile</category>
    <description>
      Lets chat is a mobile application built to provide the chat facility between users. Users need to register theirself before entering to the application and they can
      chat to another logged in persons in a ream time. I have used IonicJs framework to built the mobile layout for the application and using NodeJs as a Backend service for
      the application.
    </description>
  </project>
  <project id="pr110">
    <title>Church Prayer App</title>
    <technology>HTML5, CSS3, AngularJs, Bootstrap</technology>
    <imagepath>/img/portfolios/mobile/church.png</imagepath>
    <category>mobile</category>
    <description>
      A church prayer wall where people can enter prayers regarding their loved ones to pray for. There is a button in the app say 'Pray', on clicking on the button, it will increase a counting number and hence users can click on button to pray for the posted prayer.
    </description>
  </project>
  <project id="pr111">
    <title>E-Commerce Online Shopping</title>
    <technology>Node.Js, Angular.Js, ExpressJs, Mongodb, Bootstrap, CSS3</technology>
    <imagepath>/img/portfolios/web/e-commerce.png</imagepath>
    <category>web</category>
    <description>
      A place to buy things, its a greatest demandable website in the world. Everyone want to sell their products online and every people want to buy things online.
      I have made selling and buying functionality easy by developing this app. Users can buy, pay and get the desired product at home.
    </description>
  </project>
  <project id="pr112">
    <title>Largo (Onsite project from Ireland)</title>
    <technology>Win Forms, VB.Net, Barcode Scanner, Oracle, Label Printer</technology>
    <imagepath>/img/portfolios/windows/largo1.png</imagepath>
    <category>windows</category>
    <description>
      I developed this software in Ireland during the Onsite development. I was in Ireland for three months sent from my company. 
      This project was for a Snacks selling company in Ireland, they scan and generate the label barcode for each of their products. This project was built to provide
      a facility to read and generate the lables.
    </description>
  </project>
  <project id="pr113">
    <title>Kingfisher (Onsite project from Ireland)</title>
    <technology>Win Forms, VB.Net, Telerik Controls, Label Printer, Barcode Scanner</technology>
    <imagepath>/img/portfolios/windows/kingfisher.png</imagepath>
    <category>windows</category>
    <description>
      This project was from Ireland. This software is built to provide Kingfisher company members and their client a way to buy and sell products easily and 
      manage all the related things like Invoices, Product details, Trawlers etc in the database of the project.
      The functionality of the projects are- Scanning the label, Generating the lable, Generate invoices, manage customers, manage stocks, manage trawlers etc
    </description>
  </project>
  <project id="pr114">
    <title>Facebook Ads Report integration</title>
    <technology>Classic ASP, jQuery, Javascript, Facebook Graph APIs, VBScript, HTML5</technology>
    <imagepath>/img/portfolios/windows/facebook-api.png</imagepath>
    <category>web</category>
    <description>
      The application is developed in Classic ASP code and uses Facebook Marketing APIs to integrate the Facebook Ad reports in website. Users have their account in this application and this application reads the user's ads information from facebook and plots the chart, graph etc to display it. 
	  
	  It also uses Facebook Webhooks integration to get the realtime updates about changes happens in facebook pages, posts etc.
    </description>
  </project>
    <project id="pr115">
    <title>Onedrive Connector</title>
    <technology>Node.Js, ExpressJs, jQuery, Javascript, MS Onedrive APIs, MongoDb</technology>
    <imagepath>/img/portfolios/windows/onedrive.png</imagepath>
    <category>web</category>
    <description>
      Its a connector application which connects Onedrive Business Accounts in application using Oauth integration process. It has the functionality to Subscribe Onedrive Webhooks and after subscriptions, it gets the file changes notifications in the application. Once it gets a file change notification, it peforms some operations on the uploaded file and sends back the result to Onedrive.
    </description>
  </project>
</projects>

