<projects>
  <project id="pr101">
    <title>Online Dynamic Web Designing Tool</title>
    <technology>ASP.Net, C#, jQuery, Javascript, Bootstrap, MSSQL Server</technology>
    <imagepath>/img/portfolios/web/not-found.png</imagepath>
    <category>web</category>
    <description>
      This project was completed in B.Tech in a team of 5 members and the aim of this project was
      to provide a way to the non-technical person ability to develop website.
    </description>
  </project>
  <project id="pr102">
    <title>A website like Freelancer.com</title>
    <technology>ASP.Net, C#, jQuery, Javascript, Bootstrap, MSSQL Server</technology>
    <imagepath>/img/portfolios/web/not-found.png</imagepath>
    <category>web</category>
    <description>
      This project is the same as Freelancer.com which includes two main functions like Hire and Work.
      We developed this as a simple application during the B.Tech Industrial Training program in team of 4 members.
    </description>
  </project>
  <project id="pr103">
    <title>Claim Ruler</title>
    <technology>ASP.Net MVC 5, C#, jQuery, Javascript, Bootstrap, MSSQL Server, Database First Approach</technology>
    <imagepath>/img/portfolios/web/1.png</imagepath>
    <category>web</category>
    <description>
      This is a CRM project built on top of technologies like ASP.Net MVC, jQuery, Javascript etc and provides users facility to create Claims.
    </description>
  </project>
  <project id="pr104">
    <title>Street 2 Media</title>
    <technology>ASP.Net MVC, C#, jQuery, Javascript, Bootstrap, SQL Server</technology>
    <imagepath>/img/portfolios/web/2.png</imagepath>
    <category>web</category>
    <description>
      Put your photos and videos in front of the media and get paid! Register today and download. All the uploaded photos will be reviewed by Collaborators and will be displayed privately so that public users can pay and download.
    </description>
  </project>
  <project id="pr105">
    <title>iHRM</title>
    <technology>ASP.Net MVC, C#, jQuery, Angular.Js, Bootstrap, SQL Server</technology>
    <imagepath>/img/portfolios/web/3.png</imagepath>
    <category>web</category>
    <description>
      iHRM, an advanced leading software to manage Human Resource for a company. This project is built to provide the company a facility to create, update, delete users manage the user attendance etc.
    </description>
  </project>
  <project id="pr106">
    <title>Expense Management</title>
    <technology>Ionic, Angular.Js, Node.Js, MongoDb</technology>
    <imagepath>/img/portfolios/mobile/1.png</imagepath>
    <category>mobile</category>
    <description>
      This app is built using Ionic framework and using Node.Js service for authentication and back-end query and MongoDb is used for database storage.
    </description>
  </project>
</projects>